<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Zippy</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to\n Zippy</string>
    <string name="email_hint" translatable="false">Email</string>
    <string name="logodescricao" translatable="false">Zippy Logo</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions">By continuing, you agree to our Terms of Service and confirm that you have read our Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="criar_senha">Create your password</string>
    <string name="confirmar_senha">Confirm your password</string>
    <string name="quase_la">We are almost there..</string>
    <string name="cpf">Enter your CPF</string>
    <string name="fim">Finish</string>
    <string name="entrar">Hello again!\nSign in to proceed!</string>
    <string name="senha_hint">Password</string>
    <string name="btn_entrar">Sign in</string>
    <string name="cpf_hint">CPF</string>
    <string name="btn_continuar">Continue</string>
    <string name="esqueceu_senha">Forgot your password\?</string>
    <string name="txtOnclick_RedefinirSenha">Reset Here!</string>
    <string name="redefinir_titulo">Reset your Password</string>
    <string name="inserir_email_esqueceu_senha">Enter your email registered on our App</string>
    <string name="enviar_esqueceuSenha">To send</string>
    <string name="chat">Chat</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="txt_btn_carousel">check out</string>
    <string name="carousel_image_description">carousel_imaage</string>
    <string name="title_perfil_BB">Profile</string>
    <string name="title_chat_BB">Chat</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close Drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_config">ConfigActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="lorem_ipsum">The customer is very important, the customer will be followed by the customer. For the chocolate salad. Maurice
        life, the pain is sometimes a corporal, the laughter of the pain needs to be read, let it be a lot of real estate
        I don\'t even laugh. Maecenas was not a member except, or so it was said. The class is apt to be taciturn and friendly
        they twist the shores through our marriages, through our hymenaean projects. It is flattering for teenagers
        diam, or rutrum tellus vulputate quis Some people need free buses, financing the players from
        to decorate from But CNN is like a free portal policy. Stay in the said country.\n\n
        Sometimes the massage is done before. Some don\'t even have a course. That\'s a great recipe for disease. We live
        the need, it is a matter of need, the ugly players targeted him, but in the said region pain
        nor It was a disease of the earth, the protein was like a salad, and the targets were targeted. Sometimes it is expected
        hunger and before him the first in the throat. Curabitur et eros porttitor, ultricies urna vitae,
        salary The boat is at your advantage, and not the truck. But the biggest fans are not the pain
        he needs a drink or homework.\n\n
        But sometimes the tortor nibh, in the arrows who laughs softly. Chat my hate, let it be a story
        but the author is soft, not ugly. No free trial, for clinical purposes or
        employee than Fusce flatters no tincidunt, who cares free and easy. Complete
        now and then the law, and the fear of the ferment of the office. The bed of the bed, he said
        Lacinia is going to be fun, how sad it is. Tomorrow I will give you a result. Subscribe now
        put it in the box, but That\'s a great basketball game, in mourning. But from the kids
        is.\n\n
        Aenean wants now, but Lacinia is sad, but there is no basketball cartoon. Even from a poisoned book.
        Morbi laoreet, tortor sed facilisis varius, nibh orci rhoncus nula, id elementum leo dui
        not the internet. In fact, the author of the casino is very soft. Each element of free football is convenient. In
        eros nisl, investment or investment and, chocolate from mauris. Children are different from now on,
        who invests the money and It has two clinical purposes and is responsible for development. But not cartoons
        very Now, who wants to advertise, run a course, and be an employee. The disease will follow him, a
        place diam. Even vulputate dignissim convallis. It\'s a fun thing to do with the ends
        valley.\n\n
        Boat on my trucks. The children live in old age and grandchildren
        expected hunger and bad needs. In the life of the bow as a trigger of arrows, in the ends of the mass
        pregnant The children of that region of the hospital. It has been said in full, but it is made into a notebook,
        He will be pursued just as freely, in soft nisls from sed nisls. Until the greatest corporal
        members It\'s time to drink the earth and not the land. In a deck there is no Until CNN
        free or now the result, who can tincidunt nisl eleifend. To-morrow we must drink from a righteous mourning
        vestibule Fusce said to the libero who was the greatest, the dignistis of the career of his life.</string>
    <string name="fale_conosco_card">Talk to one of our affiliates around the WORLD</string>
    <string name="entrar_em_contato_card">Get in touch</string>
    <string name="faça_solicitação">Looking for something specific\?\nMake your request!</string>
    <string name="fazer_post">Make Post</string>
    <string name="content_Descripton">LOGO</string>
    <string name="config_drawer">settings</string>
    <string name="suporte_drawer">Support\n</string>
    <string name="sair_drawer">Log out\n</string>
    <string name="solicita_drawer">Requests</string>
    <string name="fazer_post_drawer">Make Post</string>
    <string name="slogan">Your international shopping app\n</string>
    <string name="ver_perfil_drawer">View your profile</string>

</resources>